const STORE= [
  {question: 'The full name of Naruto is...?',
  answer: ['Naruto Nara', 'Naruto Uzumaki', 'Naruto Uchiha', 'Naruto Lee'],
  correctAnswer: 'Naruto Uzumaki',
  icon: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/lNNnZpn9PhW1i/giphy.gif',
  alt: 'naruto uzumaki'},
  
  {question: 'Who is the father of Naruto?',
  answer: ['The 4th Hokage', 'Minato', 'Both of the above', 'none of the above'],
  correctAnswer: 'Both of the above',
  icon:'https://media.giphy.com/media/fNZzlhetWttyU/giphy.gif',alt: "naruto's father"},

  {question: "What is Naruto's favorite food?",
  answer: ['sushi','bbq','hamburger','ramen'],
  correctAnswer: 'ramen',
  icon:'https://media.giphy.com/media/1Q1mch6PjZIGY/giphy.gif',alt: 'naruto and rock lee eating ramen' },

  {question:'Which beast is sealed into Naruto?', 
  answer: ['9 tails', '8 tails', '3 tails', '2 tails'],
  correctAnswer: '9 tails',
  icon:'https://media.giphy.com/media/NmMZW7xzOttsI/giphy.gif',alt:'kuruma, the 9 tailed beast, sealed into naruto'},

  {question:'Who does Naruto learn "1000 years of pain" from?',
  answer: ['itachi','kakashi', 'obito', 'jiraiya'],
  correctAnswer: 'kakashi',
  icon:' https://media.giphy.com/media/Do5GRTYRIhSFy/giphy.gif',
  alt: 'kakashi performing "1000 years of pain" on naruto'},

  {question: 'Which animal does Naruto summon?',
  answer: ['slug', 'snake', 'chameleon', 'frog'],
  correctAnswer: 'frog',
  icon:' https://media.giphy.com/media/fdfEKMGoAgN44/giphy.gif',
  alt:'naruto getting spit out of the frog he summons'},

  {question: "Who is Naruto's ultimate rival?",
  answer: ['Hinata', 'Gaara', 'Sasuke', 'jiraiya'],
  correctAnswer: 'Sasuke',
  icon:'https://media.giphy.com/media/DDGoK2aFv6Mla/giphy.gif',alt: 'sasuke and naruto battling each other'},

  {question: "Which sage trains Naruto?",
  answer: ['the pervy sage', 'the snake sage', 'the sexy sage', 'the fatty sage'],
  correctAnswer: 'the pervy sage',
  icon:'https://media.giphy.com/media/Yv6RcuiyHYmn6/giphy.gif',alt:'jiraiya the "pervy sage" and naruto'},

  {question: "Which Hokage does Naruto become?",
  answer:['fifth', 'sixth', 'seventh','eighth'],
  correctAnswer:'seventh',
  icon:'https://media.giphy.com/media/ekNgxh1qaPey4/giphy.gif',alt:'naruto as 7th hokage'},

  {question: "who dies saving Hinata and Naruto?",
  answer:['kiba','shikamaru','neji','sasuke'],
  correctAnswer:'neji',
  icon:'https://media.giphy.com/media/I8EubTjoUZsUE/giphy.gif',alt:'neji'},





